<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DairyFreeDining</string>

    <!-- Navigation -->
    <string name="navigate_back">Navigate Back</string>

    <!-- Search Bar -->
    <string name="search_bar_leading">Search</string>
    <string name="search_bar_trailing">Clear</string>

    <!-- Landing Screen -->
    <string name="landing_search_bar_placeholder">Search restaurants…</string>
    <string name="no_restaurants_found">No Restaurants Found</string>

    <!-- Details Screen -->
    <string name="details_search_bar_placeholder">Search foods…</string>
    <string name="no_food_items_found">No Food Items Found</string>

    <!-- Submission Screen -->
    <string name="submission_screen">Submission</string>
    <string name="submission_screen_description">If you discover a dairy-free food item at a restaurant that you frequent, please submit this item. Upon our review, we'll update our listings with this item.</string>
    <string name="submission_screen_restaurant_label">Restaurant</string>
    <string name="submission_screen_category_label">Category</string>
    <string name="submission_screen_food_label">Food</string>
    <string name="submission_screen_button_label">Submit Food</string>
    <string name="submission_screen_error_empty_fields">Please make sure no fields are empty</string>
    <string name="submission_screen_error_network">Something went wrong…</string>
    <string name="submission_screen_success">Submitted</string>

    <!-- Loading Screen -->
    <string name="loading_screen_content">Loading…</string>

    <!-- Error Screen -->
    <string name="error_screen_content">Something went wrong…</string>
    <string name="error_screen_button_content">Try Again</string>

    <!-- About Screen -->
    <string name="about_screen">About</string>
    <string name="about_me_header">About Me</string>
    <string name="about_me_paragraph_1">Hello, I'm Kabishan, a software engineer at RBC. After discovering that dairy was the culprit behind my lifelong acne struggles, I learned that I am allergic to dairy rather than simply lactose intolerant. This realization led to the challenge of explaining my dairy-free lifestyle to family and colleagues. While my family was supportive, navigating social situations at work and family gatherings became awkward due to my dietary restrictions.</string>
    <string name="about_me_paragraph_2">To alleviate the discomfort of avoiding events where I was uncertain about the availability of dairy-free options, I created this app. Its purpose is to help users find dairy-free items conveniently, reducing the need for awkward explanations and ensuring smoother dining experiences.</string>
    <string name="credits_header">Credits</string>
    <string name="credits_content_paragraph_1">We extend our gratitude to GoDairyFree for providing an initial list of dairy-free options at popular fast food chains.</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_header">Disclaimer</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_content_paragraph_1">Please be aware that cross-contamination with dairy is a significant risk in fast food restaurants. The information provided here is for informational purposes only and should not be solely relied upon. Ingredients, menu items, and preparation processes can change frequently and without notice. While we strive to keep our list updated with the most accurate information, we cannot guarantee its completeness or accuracy. Always verify product details and preparation methods with the restaurant directly before consuming any food.</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_content_paragraph_2">If you have a severe or life-threatening food allergy to milk or other allergens, consult with a physician to discuss the appropriate level of caution when dining out.</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_content_paragraph_3">This information is sourced from restaurant chain websites, customer service representatives, or other printed materials. We have listed items identified by fast food chains as free from milk ingredients and highlighted those with a higher risk of cross-contamination. As a third-party source, we do not guarantee the accuracy of this information.</string>
</resources>